<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[From The Outer Edge - The Photography of Duncan Wallis]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[From The Outer Edge - The Photography of Duncan Wallis]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/duncan-wallis/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 10:42:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/duncan-wallis/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing Our Origins]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Capturing Our Origins</h1><p>Just another night under the stars. Astrophotography can be incredibly lonely at times, but also one of the most personally rewarding types of photography.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1d5f29306266c7127004c8386c3ffa41704d09d3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/duncan-wallis/capturing-our-origins/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b4c05bbe-5750-41d9-9857-a427668f46fb</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 10:42:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c9a58470-d6cd-423b-b3d2-85d982803a6d.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/duncan-wallis/0a9d41ad-aa96-4e0f-8c35-8c9e1b0bacd3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0a9d41ad-aa96-4e0f-8c35-8c9e1b0bacd3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 10:26:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From The Outer Edge]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>From The Outer Edge</h1><p>Welcome to the neighbourhood, our little home within our galaxy, the Milky Way. Spanning over 100, 000 lights across, there's a lot of space between our galactic core and the little rock that revolves around an unimportant star between the outer edges of the Orion and Cygnus arms that just happens to be home to everyone you have ever known or will know, ever loved and will love. In fact, at around 27,000 light years away from our galaxy's core; the light from that part of galaxy started its journey to us when as a species were still hunter-gatherers. Just as we revolve our sun, it in turn revolves our galactic core (and us with it). The last time our sun was in its current position was around 250,000,000 years ago whilst the dinosaurs still roamed our planet and we as a species didn't even exist. Keep that in mind when you think that humans will be around forever, look at what has occurred just on our little planet in the time that it's taken our sun to complete one of it's galactic years. With the little time that we all have to inhabit this finite planet, I hope that we can pursue our dreams, make our home last a little longer and appreciate just how insignificantly small we are within the universe whilst being part of something much larger than any of us could ever imagine.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9cc75eef3fd73cc3139454f94a2d507ff0bba3df.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/duncan-wallis/welcome-to-the-outer-edge/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88d87a64-e86c-4626-b7f8-b23bd5186c72</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 10:40:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>